martinmadsen

graduate student of computer science

about

Myrdalstræde 43D, 1, 2 9220 Aalborg Øst Denmark

23 years old +45 26 27 36 60 me@martinbmadsen.dk martinbmadsen.dk

martinbjeldbak

in / martinbjeldbak martinbjeldbak

f / martinbjeldbak

/ martinbjeldbak

languages

bilingual danish/english

programming

Ruby, Python JavaScript, Express.js C, C#, Java SQL LATEX, HTML, CSS3 Git. SVN Haskell (learning) Software engineering OS X, Unix

interests

machine learning TDD, functional programming web development healthcare automotive industry

education

since 2014 M.Sc. in Computer Science Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark Majoring in Computer Science (120 ECTS) Specializing in Machine Intelligence 2014-2015 Studying abroad University of California, San Diego Accredited as part of the first year of my master's degree from Aalborg University 2011-2014 **B.Sc.** in Computer Science Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark Majoring in Computer Science (180 ECTS)

experience

2008-2011

2012-2014 **Student Software Developer**

Student

Falck Healthcare a/s

Development of Ruby on Rails-based system used daily by ca. 40 of Falck's physiotherapists to journal their patients' treatments and wellbeing.

2010-2014 Founder Divambu (shut down)

Ran my own small company developing and hosting web sites for clients.

other activities

2013-2014 Student member of the Study Board

Focus in physics and engineering

Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark

EUC Nord - Technical Gymnasium of Hjørring

Elected position. Handling of educations within Computer Science curricula at the university, quality assurance of education, handling of exemptions, etc.

Volunteer mentor 2012-2014

Projekt Solskinsunge 2012

We arranged bi-monthly social gatherings for teenagers aged 15-18, most of who were second generation immigrants.

projects

2015	XQuery Processor UC San Diego Implemented a subset of the XQuery and XPa	o, \(\Gamma\) martinbjeldbak/xquery-processor th XML query languages in Java.
2014	Diversity Measurement in Genetic Algorithms Concluded my B.Sc. degree. Currently in the	AAU, martinbmadsen.dk/bachelor.pdf process of getting published.
2014	OpenTracker Rails app and corresponding Python plugin for the racing simulator video game Assetto Corsa, allowing anyone to view location and information of racers on track in real-time.	

...and many others! I contribute as much as I can to open source and work on other projects for fun. For more examples, feel free to check out my GitHub profile linked above.